Risqué is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Tony Dean Smith.
Fired from a strip club, a vengeful dancer masterminds a high-stakes heist with fellow
strippers to take down the corrupt boss and the men who underestimate them.
Jessica, played by Leah Gibson.
Shelby, played by Eloise Lovell Anderson.
Carmen, played by Silvia Orduna.
Bianka, played by Rex Adams.
Kiko, played by Julia Strowski.
Mike, played by David Thomas Newman.
Masti (English translation: Fun) is a 2004 Indian Hindi-language adult comedy film directed by Indra Kumar, starring Ajay
Devgn, Vivek Oberoi, Riteish Deshmukh, Aftab Shivdasani, Lara Dutta, Amrita Rao, Tara Sharma, and Genelia.
The film was released in 2004, and received positive responses from
critics, and also managed to do well at the box office.
The film spawned three sequels, Grand Masti (2013), Great
Grand Masti (2016) and Mastiii 4 (2025).
The film explores themes of stripper, heist, revenge thriller.
The tone is intense.